question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo co-pilot and best friend, Chewbacca, is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The movie The Nightmare before Christmas was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet "
                 "in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The 2010 film The Social Network is a biographical "
                 "drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Shaquille Neal appeared in the 1997 film Space Jam.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio character hunts down the killer of his son.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
